Young Master.
المعلم الصغير.
Young Master, you're finally back.
سيد الشباب ، لقد عدت أخيرًا.
Young Lady
إمرأة شابة
didn't come back yesterday.
لم يعد بالأمس.
I know.
أنا أعرف.
What to do?
ماذا أفعل؟
Young Lady won't be abducted by bad people, right?
لن يتم اختطاف السيدة الصغيرة من قبل الأشرار ، أليس كذلك؟
What if she's abducted by the traffickers?
ماذا لو اختطفها المهربون؟
Young Master.
المعلم الصغير.
Did you look for Young Lady?
هل بحثت عن السيدة الصغيرة؟
Why should he look for her?
لماذا يبحث عنها؟
Should we bring her back to Ling's Residence
هل يجب أن نعيدها إلى سكن لينج
and let her hurt everyone once more?
ودعها تؤذي الجميع مرة أخرى؟
You...
أنت...
Ye.
انتم.
Don't be fooled by that woman again.
لا تنخدع بهذه المرأة مرة أخرى.
We don't even know if this is Young Lady's fault.
لا نعرف حتى ما إذا كان هذا خطأ السيدة الشابة.
Why are you putting the blame on her now?
لماذا تلقي اللوم عليها الآن؟
Then, go and look for her.
ثم اذهب وابحث عنها.
I hope she didn't flee
آمل ألا تهرب
to avoid her punishment.
لتجنب عقابها.
You...
أنت...
Stop it.
توقف عن ذلك.
Ye, I feel sad for you.
أجل ، أشعر بالحزن من أجلك.
You don't know,
انت لا تعلم
but Zhou Han came to me too.
لكن زو هان جاء لي أيضًا.
He told me personally
قال لي شخصيا
that that woman
تلك تلك المرأة
is a spy sent by him.
هو جاسوس أرسله.
He even asked me to join them.
حتى أنه طلب مني الانضمام إليهم.
How shameless he is!
كم هو وقح!
Did he really say that?
هل قال ذلك حقا؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
What they said was worse than what I just said.
ما قالوه كان أسوأ مما قلته للتو.
Ye.
انتم.
Don't be fooled by them again.
لا تنخدع بهم مرة أخرى.
No matter how you think
لا يهم كيف تعتقد
about this incident,
عن هذه الحادثة ،
it's definitely related to that woman.
إنه مرتبط بالتأكيد بتلك المرأة.
Do you also think that she is related to this incident?
هل تعتقد أيضًا أنها مرتبطة بهذا الحادث؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
Ye.
انتم.
Don't be sad.
لا تحزن.
Even if she's not here, I'm still here.
حتى لو لم تكن هنا ، ما زلت هنا.
Ye.
انتم.
Actually,
في الحقيقة،
I've been in love with you for a long time.
لقد كنت في حبك لفترة طويلة.
I will not betray...
لن أخون ...
Ye, wait for me!
انتظرني!
[The Blessed Bride] [Episode 18]
[العروس المباركة] [الحلقة 18]
Sir, why are you so happy?
لماذا انت سعيد جدا يا سيدي؟
Can I not be happy?
لا أستطيع أن أكون سعيدا؟
It's not that.
انها ليست التي.
Sir.
سيد.
Miss Liuying
ملكة جمال Liuying
had cut ties with us.
قطع العلاقات معنا.
In the future,
فى المستقبل،
who else can help us bring down the Ling family?
من يمكنه مساعدتنا في إسقاط عائلة لينغ؟
Since no one can help us,
بما أنه لا أحد يستطيع مساعدتنا ،
seems like it's time
يبدو أن الوقت قد حان
for me to take action.
بالنسبة لي لاتخاذ إجراءات.
[The Scheming Pregnant Mother Runs Away: Mommy, Run!]
[تهرب الأم الحامل المخططة: ماما ، اهرب!]
(`There is no place for me in the Ling family now.)
(لا مكان لي في عائلة لينغ الآن).
(And I don't know when would the poison take effect.)
(ولا أعرف متى سيصبح السم ساري المفعول).
(If Zhou Han uses me to do something to the Ling family again,)
(إذا استخدمني Zhou Han لفعل شيء لعائلة Ling مرة أخرى ،)
(I'll be even more embarrassed then.)
(سأكون أكثر إحراجًا بعد ذلك).
Young Lady!
إمرأة شابة!
Young Lady, you're finally back!
سيدة شابة ، لقد عدت أخيرًا!
Young Lady.
إمرأة شابة.
Are you leaving?
هل أنت ذاهب؟
I did something wrong to the Ling family.
لقد فعلت شيئًا خاطئًا لعائلة لينغ.
I feel ashamed to stay here.
أشعر بالخجل من البقاء هنا.
Don't cry.
لا تبكي.
It's not like you can't see me anymore.
ليس الأمر كما لو أنك لا تستطيع رؤيتي بعد الآن.
But you must take care of yourself
لكن يجب أن تعتني بنفسك
when you're alone.
متى تكونين وحدك.
Young Lady.
إمرأة شابة.
Did you really do it?
هل فعلتها حقا؟
I don't believe it.
لا أصدق ذلك.
Although I didn't do it,
على الرغم من أنني لم أفعل ذلك ،
I do have something to do with it.
لدي شيء لأفعله به.
Young Lady.
إمرأة شابة.
Can you not leave?
لا يمكنك المغادرة؟
Please don't leave me here alone.
من فضلك لا تتركني وحدي هنا.
Jinse, stop crying.
جينسي ، توقف عن البكاء.
Young Lady.
إمرأة شابة.
You troublemaker!
أنت مثيري الشغب!
You're finally leaving.
أنت تغادر أخيرًا.
Young Lady is not a troublemaker!
السيدة الشابة ليست مثيري الشغب!
Look at what she did to the Ling family.
انظر إلى ما فعلته لعائلة لينغ.
She caused them to have lost so much money.
لقد تسببت في خسارة الكثير من المال لهم.
If she isn't a troublemaker,
إذا لم تكن مثيري الشغب ،
who else is?
من هو ايضا؟
You...
أنت...
Jinse.
لك.
Listen to me.
استمع لي.
Go out first.
اخرج أولا.
I'll be fine.
سأكون بخير.
If I don't leave,
إذا لم أغادر ،
are you
أنت
going to make me stay?
ستجعلني أبقى؟
Of course not.
بالطبع لا.
The earlier you leave,
في وقت مبكر تغادر ،
the earlier Ye doesn't have to see you.
في وقت سابق لا داعي لرؤيتك.
So, hurry up and leave.
لذا ، أسرع وغادر.
Wait a minute.
انتظر دقيقة.
I must check your bag carefully.
يجب أن أفحص حقيبتك بعناية.
In case, you bring
في حالة إحضار
something that you shouldn't.
شيء لا يجب عليك.
Go ahead.
إنطلق.
Feel free to take a look.
تفضل ألقي نظرة.
Make sure you let me know when you're done.
تأكد من إخباري عند الانتهاء.
"The Overbearing Prince Is In Love With Me"?
"الأمير الجبار يحبني"؟
This is the kind of book you usually read?
هذا هو نوع الكتاب الذي تقرأه عادة؟
Who can prove
من يستطيع أن يثبت
that I didn't do this?
أنني لم أفعل هذا؟
[Adapted from the comic "My Dear Concubine" drawn by Ah Weiwei and Muxi Huanhuan]
[مقتبس من الفيلم الكوميدي "My Dear Concubine" الذي رسمه Ah Weiwei و Muxi Huanhuan]
♪Looking pretty in the wedding gown, I'm forced to get married♪
♪ أبدو جميلة في ثوب الزفاف ، أجبرت على الزواج ♪
♪Within these high walls, can I escape after having met you?♪
♪ داخل هذه الأسوار العالية هل أستطيع الهروب بعد أن التقيت بك؟ ♪
♪Late at night, I can't fall asleep with so much sadness♪
♪ في وقت متأخر من الليل ، لا أستطيع النوم مع الكثير من الحزن
♪Despite the many restrictions, I live a carefree life♪
على الرغم من القيود العديدة ، أعيش حياة خالية من الهموم
♪Turns out my mood will be much better with you around♪
♪ تبين أن مزاجي سيكون أفضل بكثير معك حولك
♪Seeing your smile, I will not run away from here again♪
برؤية ابتسامتك لن أهرب من هنا مرة أخرى
♪Enjoying the sunset in the bamboo forest, your face crosses my mind♪
استمتع بغروب الشمس في غابة الخيزران ، وجهك يخطر ببالي ♪
♪I'm falling for you gradually although I say otherwise♪
♪ أنا أقع في حبك تدريجياً رغم أنني أقول غير ذلك ♪
♪I'd like to say♪
♪ أود أن أقول ♪
♪I want this to be sweet and romantic between us♪
♪ اريد ان يكون هذا حلو ورومانسي بيننا
♪I want to marry you and grow old with you so badly♪
♪ أريد أن أتزوجك وأكبر معك بشدة
♪I want to witness the beauty of this world with you♪
♪ اريد ان اشهد جمال هذا العالم معك
♪Never mind that time passes and our hairs turn gray♪
♪ لا تهتم بمرور الوقت وشعرنا يتحول إلى اللون الرمادي
♪I want this to be sweet and romantic between us♪
♪ اريد ان يكون هذا حلو ورومانسي بيننا
♪I want to marry you and grow old with you so badly♪
♪ أريد أن أتزوجك وأكبر معك بشدة
♪I want to witness the beauty of this world with you♪
♪ اريد ان اشهد جمال هذا العالم معك
♪Looking pretty in the wedding gown, I'm forced to get married♪
♪ أبدو جميلة في ثوب الزفاف ، أجبرت على الزواج ♪
♪Within these high walls, can I escape after having met you?♪
♪ داخل هذه الأسوار العالية هل أستطيع الهروب بعد أن التقيت بك؟ ♪
♪Late at night, I can't fall asleep with so much sadness♪
♪ في وقت متأخر من الليل ، لا أستطيع النوم مع الكثير من الحزن
♪Despite the many restrictions, I live a carefree life♪
على الرغم من القيود العديدة ، أعيش حياة خالية من الهموم
♪Turns out my mood will be much better with you around♪
♪ تبين أن مزاجي سيكون أفضل بكثير معك حولك
♪Seeing your smile, I will not run away from here again♪
برؤية ابتسامتك لن أهرب من هنا مرة أخرى
♪Enjoying the sunset in the bamboo forest, your face crosses my mind♪
استمتع بغروب الشمس في غابة الخيزران ، وجهك يخطر ببالي ♪
♪I'm falling for you gradually although I say otherwise♪
♪ أنا أقع في حبك تدريجياً رغم أنني أقول غير ذلك ♪
♪I'd like to say♪
♪ أود أن أقول ♪
♪I want this to be sweet and romantic between us♪
♪ اريد ان يكون هذا حلو ورومانسي بيننا
♪I want to marry you and grow old with you so badly♪
♪ أريد أن أتزوجك وأكبر معك بشدة
♪I want to witness the beauty of this world with you♪
♪ اريد ان اشهد جمال هذا العالم معك
♪Never mind that time passes and our hairs turn gray♪
♪ لا تهتم بمرور الوقت وشعرنا يتحول إلى اللون الرمادي
♪I want this to be sweet and romantic between us♪
♪ اريد ان يكون هذا حلو ورومانسي بيننا
♪I want to marry you and grow old with you so badly♪
♪ أريد أن أتزوجك وأكبر معك بشدة
♪I want to witness the beauty of this world with you♪
♪ اريد ان اشهد جمال هذا العالم معك
♪Never mind that time passes and our hairs turn gray♪
♪ لا تهتم بمرور الوقت وشعرنا يتحول إلى اللون الرمادي
[The Blessed Bride]
[العروس المباركة]
[Adapted from "My Dear Concubine" on Cloud Comic]
[مقتبس من "My Dear Concubine" on Cloud Comic]